[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINES REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Someone could've died!
We overstepped, sir!
Before you scold me...
let's not forget
who ordered the demolition
in Ginintuang Lupa.
It's your father, isn't it?
- Gentlemen!
- We exercised
maximum tolerance.
But a civilian was shot!
I don't know how you'll fix this
but you better fix it!
She's looking for a job.
Your family committed
an offense against ours.
How bold of you
to even come to me.
Whatever happened between Gabo
and Django
has nothing to do with me!
Rudy just really needs it!
- For his funeral?
- For the hospital!
I have a meeting
at Jade Imperial.
The target is on his way out.
- Visuals on target.
- Let's follow him.
Follow Mr. Chan.
I'll be right behind you.
I'll just get my bike.
I'll see you at Jade Imperial.
- [THUDS]
- [GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
We're done for.
The issue's already reached
the higher-ups.
We wouldn't be having an issue
if it weren't for that Salvador.
What do you want, sir?
- Want me to get rid of him?
- No.
Not yet.
Eyes are still on us.
They'll blame us for sure
if anything happens to him.
Just give him a little scare.
Huh?
So he'll learn.
Aye, sir. I'll give him
a little nudge.
- Umali.
- Yes, sir.
Let someone else do it, okay?
I don't want to deal with
any loose ends.
- Copy, sir.
- Sir.
How about the other problem?
The civilian who got shot.
Send Lieutenant Jacinto here.
If we're going to give someone
a scare,
then we need
to coax someone else.
[LAUGHS]
Yes, sir.
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
Excuse me, sir.
You called for me?
Yes. Lieutenant Jacinto, please.
General Duran rushed here
because of the...
controversies about
the demolition
of Ginintuang Lupa.
I didn't do anything wrong,
did I?
Answer.
No, sir.
I just followed
your father's orders.
And because of that, it could
affect my career.
Do you think I deserve that,
Lieutenant Jacinto?
Answer.
No, sir.
You don't deserve that.
I just followed orders
because I am a good soldier
and now...
I'm the one getting caught
in the middle of it all.
I couldn't do anything.
Is there anything...
that you or your family could do
to prevent the situation
from blowing up
[DOMINGO SIGHS]
even more?
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
I understand, sir.
You don't deserve this.
So I want to pay you back
for the favor you did
for my father.
Thank you, Lieutenant Jacinto.
Thank you.
Ma'am.
[SIGHS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[CHAIR SCRAPING]
[SIGHS]
Ma'am, are you alright?
You seem troubled.
Did the Colonel say anything?
Colonel Domingo was scolded
by General Duran
for that viral interview.
The Colonel was the one
who got scolded,
but why do you look bothered?
I was just thinking...
Our unit is the reason why
the image of NLEA
is being ruined.
So you know, even if it's wrong,
I have to help Colonel Domingo
with this problem.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey.
It's Tonyo!
- Tonyo!
- Hi, Tonyo!
Gosh.
He's stingy with money.
It's better than nothing.
Tonyo, will you book
a table with us?
I am looking
for a good meal.
- Oh!
- But...
It seems like the food here
is spoiled.
Watch how you speak!
Take a look t yourself!
You went here drunk,
but not with our drinks!
I'm trying to save money!
I came here drunk so you'll all
look beautiful in my eyes
But I don't think it worked.
Wow!
Look at you, Tonyo!
I'll pray for you
so you look more handsome!
He's hopeless.
Betchay, you don't look
spoiled at all.
You're stale!
[LAUGHTER]
Fine, I'll get a table with you.
Now we're talking!
Tonyo!
Shh! Aya!
[ISOBEL GASPS] Twinkle!
- That should already be set up.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Mom.
- Oh!
- Hi.
- Max.
- Hi, Mom.
- Hmm.
How's work?
I want to say its okay,
but it's not.
It's because of the people
in Ginintuang Lupa.
Oh my God.
They already filed for a TRO
to stop the demolition.
I mean, what other
countermeasure do they need?
Dad, you don't have
to worry about this.
But I want to let you know
that I'm going to settle
with the victim's family.
Um...
Max, that place is dangerous.
My people are already moving
to fix the problem.
And we will not settle
with anyone.
Dad, let me do this
for the family.
Especially for you.
[ISOBEL] Max.
If you have a solution
and you're planning to go there,
just don't let them know
that you're a cop.
Or a Jacinto.
You'll surely get in trouble.
Mom.
At least, just...
let me talk to that woman.
The one in the news.
She's ruining our reputation.
Including our family-- our name!
What woman on the news?
What are you talking about, Max?
[TWINKLE] Ma'am Max,
I know about her!
She's doing too much!
I saw her on the news.
- She just wants to be viral.
- Exactly.
Wait. I'm lost.
Who's this girl
you're talking about?
What is this?
[MAX] Haven't you seen
the news, Mom?
Toto and I have seen it.
Where? Let me see it.
- Show it to them.
- Toto!
Toto!
- Sweetie...
- Hurry up!
- Sweetie.
- Show it to sir!
- Hurry!
- Let me see. C'mon.
- Here you go, sir.
- What's that? Let me see.
[SALVADOR] After we interviewed
a woman whose husband,
Rudy Magtibay,
is currently in critical
condition at the hospital.
One question remains
in the family's mind,
who fired the shot?
Who is to blame for this?
We will never stop pursuing this
until whoever is responsible
is held accountable.
This is Salvador
"Benggador" Manalo.
Standing by the oppressed.
This is Telebalita.
[ISOBEL] How dare they!
What's all this fuss
when they're in the wrong?!
[MAX] Exactly, Ma.
So let me do this because
this woman won't stop.
She's looking for money
so she can shut up.
- And you, Twinkle. Come here.
- Ma'am.
Next time you hear any
news about us,
let us know right away!
Yes, ma'am.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You're lucky you survived, Rudy.
But karma will surely
get you back.
I myself will ensure that you
and your loved ones
pay for the wrongs
you've done to me.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey, one bottle of beer please!
Don't you want
to order any bar chow?
Not even fish crackers
or peanuts?
Let me tell you this,
the best bar chow
is conversations.
Anything you want to share?
Conversation? [SCOFFS]
[CLEARS THROAT] Okay.
[SPEAKERS PLAYING
DOWNBEAT MUSIC]
- It's about Rudy--
- Oh!
I'm done.
I'm bored
with your story already.
I haven't even said a thing!
I got an idea.
Just dance.
You want me to dance?
I only had one beer.
Oh, please, you're crazy.
Fine then.
I'll sing and you'll dance.
No, Tonyo, no.
- Let's just talk.
- Come on.
- I'll sing. Miss! Miss!
- Tonyo!
- Hey! Go back here!
- Can I borrow a mic?
I'll tell you a story!
This one's for you!
- [BETCHAY] Shhh!
- [TONYO SINGING] Betchay
- Your thighs are so thick
- Stop singing.
[TONYO]
Your legs are full of veins
[BETCHAY] Enough! Shhh!
Let's just talk.
Tonyo, please!
Fine, I'll dance.
Just stop singing. There.
Put some energy into it!
You know what, I'm done.
No, no, please don't.
- Aya!
- [AYA] What?
[TONYO] Aya!
- Why?
- [TONYO] Let's go!
Baby, come to papa!
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Give me a good time.
Betchay is useless.
Absolutely!
- [TONYO] Where should we go?
- [AYA] Oh, let's go there.
I'll give you
a good time, darling.
What happened?
Oh, Tonyo is such a pain
to deal with!
You're good.
That's just the way it is.
When they're drunk,
they're easy.
It's okay.
More men are coming, right?
For sure.
Betchay!
Oh, Paquito, sorry!
That wasn't my fault.
Please give me another chance--
Sit down.
We'll talk.
[PAQUITO GRUNTS]
Why did you ask me to sit?
I want you to keep me company.
Don't you want to?
You're making fun of me.
You're unbelievable.
You know I'm desperate,
and you're making fun of me.
You're unbelievable, Paquito.
I know you're not the problem
as to why no customer wants you.
It's on the customer.
I need money,
not someone to talk to.
Hmm.
You need money, you say?
There.
You can have that.
- Really?
- Yes.
You know what, Betchay...
[BOTTLE CAP CLICKS]
I've liked you for a long time.
I've liked you
since we were young.
The problem was that
Rudy made a move on you first.
What did you even see
in that guy?
For me, he's handsome.
You picked him. Now what?
He brought you misfortune.
And you have a stepson
who's an ex-convict.
You are with a man
who has achieved
nothing in life.
Tell me.
Is there anyone here
in Ginintuang Lupa
who has been successful?
Me.
Betchay, I'm the king
of this place.
I've passed the throne
to Django.
The problem is your stepson,
Gabo, wants that title too.
Tell him off.
Because when our paths cross,
I won't go easy on him.
[BETCHAY SCOFFS]
Leave me out of that.
Do whatever you want to him.
He's such a pain to Rudy and me.
He's a troublemaker.
Really?
You're giving me permission
to beat up Gabo
until he turns purple?
Why do you need to ask me?
I thought you're a thug?
You're right.
Let's... let's just drink.
I'm paying.
[BOTTLES CLINK]
[FIREWORKS WHOOSHING, CRACKING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[SEBASTIAN]
We're about to go in.
Make sure
everything goes smoothly.
Sure, sure.
We'll take care of it.
- [DIGITAL TRILLING]
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
That's the place.
That one.
Come on, come on.
- Where's your invitation, sir?
- What?
[BONG] Invitation?
Is it someone's birthday?
- [BOUNCER] Here, it's this.
- Don't you remember me?
Sir, ma'am, you need to have
a QR code to get in.
Here, here.
They're with me...
- [UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Mr. Chan, welcome back!
The usual. Expensive.
Right away, sir.
Mr. Chan, you can wait
and relax here.
Put the box there.
Have a seat.
Make yourself at home.
[CAR APPROACHING]
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
[TEKLA] Hey! Say sorry!
[BOUNCER]
You're bothering the guests.
[TOLITS]
There's no one coming in!
What's the problem?
[IPE] We got here first.
[BINOY] What's the thing
they're showing?
[SCANNER BEEPS, CHIMES]
[BINOY] It's not working!
Accommodate us first!
[SEBASTIAN]
The QR code isn't working?
- Fix it! Hurry up!
- I'm trying!
- I'm working on it.
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[MUSIC TURNS TENSE]
- [MONITOR BEEPS]
- All good.
Here, try it again.
[SCANNER BEEPS]
[EXHALES]
- Thank you.
- We're actually with them.
[BINOY]
Can we share a table with you?
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SEBASTIAN]
We'll look for Mr. Chan.
Alert us
once you see Tiger, okay?
Let's split up.
We'll check upstairs.
Let's go.
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
- [TOLITS] Gabo is here.
- [DABOY] There he is.
- [BONG] Gabo!
- [BINOY] Gabo!
- Gabo.
Well? Did you follow
Mr. Chan?
- We couldn't get in.
- Why?
We need the "QT"
to get inside.
- Silly! It's QR, not QT!
- That's what I heard.
We need to get inside.
Tiger could be inside.
What should we do now?
What's your plan?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Follow me.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[HELMET STRAP CLICKS]
Let's split up.
Find a way to get inside.
We'll meet upstairs.
Be careful, Gabo.
- This way!
- Let's go!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[METAL CLINKING]
[GABO GRUNTS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CLOTHES RUSTLING]
- [TEKLA GASPS] Hide!
- Hey!
- Take cover!
- Hide!
[SILLY MUSIC PLAYING]
How do we get inside?
- Yeah.
- We're doomed.
Look at us. We look like
we've been through hell.
Hey, speak for yourself!
Don't involve me!
I've found us a solution.
What?
Right there!
What, the washing machine?
- Huh?
- No.
I mean, that!
[SILLY MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [DABOY] Tekla!
- What?
- You take care of it!
- Stay quiet, okay?
Yeah.
[WHISPERS] Stay out of sight!
Hi, handsome!
- [GASPS]
- [GIGGLES]
Poor you.
Are you working all alone?
- Yeah.
- Will you fold all of this?
Want me to help you?
Okay.
[TEKLA] You know, you're exactly
my type of guy.
- [TOLITS WHISPERS] Let's go!
- A hardworking man.
- [MAN] Oh, really?
- [TEKLA] Totally!
[TEKLA SIGHS SOFTLY]
Come on, handsome.
Let's fold them all together.
- Sure thing.
- I'll help you.
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [TEKLA GIGGLING]
Hey!
Let's go!
- [TEKLA] I'll be your partner.
- Put them all inside!
- [BINOY] Take the comforter!
- Get to work!
- [IPE] Yes, sir.
- Do that first, okay?
- Hurry up a little.
- Don't forget the comforter!
- [TEKLA] Bye!
- Bring it in!
[SILLY MUSIC CONTINUES]
I got nervous there.
- Where do we put this?
- [CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
- Excuse me.
- Right here!
- I'll try that on.
- I really like this one.
- Can we take this home?
- Hey!
Stop playing around!
Let me think.
- Grab these!
- Huh?
- Come on, we'll pretend--
- Black?
We'll pretend to be waiters!
- I'll just be bossed around!
- Drop the diva act!
- Or you'll see!
- Where's mine?
It's an all-black outfit.
Just lose the extras!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [MUSIC BECOMES UPBEAT]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[WHOOPING, CHEERING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Bye, handsome!
- [MAN] Bye, miss!
[BINOY] Hey, remember
to separate the colors!
- [FIRE FLARING]
- [CHEF] My goodness!
What the heck is this?
We've got tons of clients!
They've been waiting
for the food!
Any update on the sea bass,
the salmon?
Where's the garnish?
Hurry up!
What a bunch of slowpokes!
My goodness!
Focus on your stations!
All of you! Stop bunching up!
Pick up the pace!
You, come here! I need you here!
- [CHEF] Move faster!
- She wants you!
- Yes, you! Come here!
- Go, go!
Come on, hurry up!
Top these with icing now!
- Hurry!
- Yes, Chef!
You, come here!
- Me? What?
- Work on these vegetables!
- Huh?
- My goodness!
We're still missing garnish!
- What do I do?
- Blanch them and chop them!
- Where do I put these?
- Geez, are you new here?
Put them over there!
Go, start chopping!
You, clean up the mess here!
The three of you! Hurry!
- She meant us.
- Here!
Serve those to Table 3!
- Come on, hurry!
- O-Okay, okay!
Walk that way!
- You two!
- Yes?
Make sure the customers
get them!
Move faster!
We've got tons of guests!
[UPBEAT MUSIC RESUMES]
[GUEST CHEERING]
[BODIES THUD]
- You okay?
- Sorry.
Just chill, okay?
Sorry again, dude.
[CROWD CHEERING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WOMEN WHOOPING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
We're almost there.
We have the item.
Mr. Chan,
I'll meet them downstairs.
Okay. I'll wait here.
Don't let other people in.
[BODYGUARD] Yes, ma'am.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC RESUMES]
[CROWD WHOOPING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
See? We made it to the party!
Why are you dancing?
We're waiters here!
Oh, right.
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
I've been looking for you.
Bring to this Mr. Chan
upstairs in the VIP room.
- Hurry up.
- Okay, sir.
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Gabo! Gabo!
Well?
Have you seen Mr. Chan?
Oh, Mr. Chan?
He's in the VIP room.
I'm actually bringing
this alcohol to him.
See if the Tiger has arrived
and let us know.
Okay, I'll keep you updated.
Wait here.
Gabo.
Are you really sure
about this job?
I'm worried.
Looks like they're
a big-time syndicate.
I just hope
the money's worth it.
Our lives could be
at stake, Gabo!
I told you not to come along,
but you insisted.
I-It's not like that!
You know we need money, too.
It just doesn't feel right.
They're heavily armed,
while we're coming in
empty-handed.
Why be scared?
We've got Gabo!
He can handle them no problem!
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Sir, here's the bottle
of special alcohol you ordered--
- Put it there!
- Okay.
[BOTTLE, GLASS THUD]
Sir, are you alone?
No one's with you?
None of your business! Go!
- Oh, s-sorry...
- Go, go!
I'm going.
[CROWD CHEERING]
[TOLITS] Gabo! Gabo!
So, is the Tiger inside or what?
Negative.
Only Mr. Chan's in the room.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You guys stay downstairs.
I'll wait up here.
As soon as the Tiger shows up,
signal me immediately.
- Now, go!
- Okay, sure!
- Let's go, let's go!
- See you around.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR ENGINES REVVING]
[BRAKE SQUEALS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CLUB MUSIC BLARING]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
Sir, Mr. Chan
is waiting for you.
Let's not keep him waiting.
[CLUB MUSIC CONTINUES BLARING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Tiger is the leader
of the biggest gold smuggling
syndicate in the country.
They have gold bars
and millions of money inside!
There's just a bit of a problem.
He's got tons of
armed bodyguards.
Trying to capture him now
is basically suicide.
Victor Zafra, hands in the air!
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[GUNSHOTS]
I need backup!
Send them to Twin Phoenix! Now!
- [TIRES SCREECH]
- [ENGINES REVVING]
- Don't let them catch you!
- I know! Shut up!
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE ROARS]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
[BRAKES, TIRES SQUEALING]
[BLOWS LAND]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- [KICKS LAND]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
[LOUD CRASH]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]